Barusu.
How long do you intend to sleep?
Wake up already, Barusu.
Bororokka?!
Where are we?
The air is still and cool.
We're most likely underground.
Ram?
You say we're underground?
Beneath the dunes.
If you believe what Lady Beatrice
said before we were separated,
it's probably because of
a distortion in space.
And that sent us flying?
Wait, separated? That's right!
Where are the others?
Why is it just you and me here?
You're asking me that?
I don't see Lady Emilia or Lady Beatrice.
You really blew it this time.
Is this really the time for that?!
We have to find the others...
No, wait... Rem...
Barusu.
We need to find all of
them, but Rem comes first!
She can't even move on her own!
We have to... We have to find her, quick!
Barusu, calm down.
Calm down?! You expect me to calm down?!
Don't you even care that Rem's in danger?!
You know I do!
You're right.
Sorry. I mean it.
I was being dumb... and a total jerk.
That's nothing new.
Anyway, I can feel my faint link with Rem.
I don't know where she is,
but she's alive, at least.
Oh, yeah!
The synesthesia you have as twins!
I see ya woke up, Natsuki.
Lady Anastasia and... Patrasche?
Sorry I borrowed her without askin'.
Even I didn't have the guts
to go lookin' around alone.
I mean, that's fine, but...
I never said it was
just the two of us here.
How did the surroundings look?
Not good. I didn't see an exit
or any of the others close by.
Looks like only us three were sent here...
Oh, and Patrasche, of course.
Just us?
No point in crying over it.
Since the useless Barusu is awake now,
let's go look for Rem and Lady Emilia.
Look for them?
I'm sensing some malice
behind this team formation!
None of us can fight!
I think... I can feel a
breeze... or maybe not...
Can't you speak with spirits, Barusu?
Lesser spirits to guide us, huh?
Problem with that is, my link with Beako
is so strong it scares lesser spirits.
Well, you're only a half-baked magician
born of Lady Beatrice's pity, after all.
Don't worry. I had no expectations.
Grr...
Natsuki.
She's trying bravely to hide it,
but right after we were sent
here, before you woke up,
Ram was pretty distraught 'cause
she didn't see Rem around.
Really?
So you're playin' a part in
keepin' her emotionally stable.
You ain't useless.
The path splits here.
As if it's telling us to
agonize over the choice.
What do we do?
Based on the knowledge I have,
Freud said that in times like
this, you always go right.
Who even is that?
Apparently, behavioral studies suggest
that humans tend to choose the left.
So my sense of justice tells
me to check the right!
You really trust this Freud a lot.
Again, who even is that?
A door?
It's huge, and it looks thick.
Can we move it?
I think that'll be tough.
Looks like it's completely sealed.
Although, Natsuki...
why do ya think this is a door?
It just looks like an iron wall to me.
Huh?
Agreed.
It just looks like a pile of
iron scrap blocking my path.
W-Well... I just thought it
kinda looked like a door...
Huh?
Eh?
What was that?
Natsuki, did you do somethin'?
Did I... You were watching, weren't you?
I only touched it!
I didn't do anything.
I don't know what happened, either.
Let's go.
Patrasche?
I know you're trying to protect us.
But in the situation we're
in, nowhere is safe.
We need to be prepared to
take risks at some point,
and now is that time.
She's got you whipped.
If there's gotta be whipping
between me and a woman,
I'd rather be the one to be whipped.
Pervert.
I didn't mean it that way!
That's two of them.
And this one just vanished, too.
What's the point in walls that
don't stop anyone's progress?
What is it?
Well, we haven't seen any yet,
so it might be hard to imagine,
but maybe they're meant
to keep mabeasts out.
There's a chance that this could be
connected to a sandworm's tunnel, too.
They may be intended to keep
only mabeasts from passing.
Yikes. If that's what it
is, that's terrifying.
Does anyone else feel weirdly heavy?
But I guess this isn't
the time for whining.
It's a little hard to walk,
but it's no big deal.
If we keep up this pace, our
goal might be closer than we—
Barusu.
Shut up.
Uh... Oh, right...
But it seems so boring to just keep quiet.
You think we're walking for fun?
Remember our objective.
Well...
Natsuki, that's enough.
Look at our situation.
When people are feelin' irritable,
nothin' ya say to anyone
is gonna end well.
Right?
Damn it!
After all this?! What the hell?!
You let us pass through three doors!
Why get in our way now?!
Damn it! Damn it! Damn it all!
Natsuki, that's enough.
We've hit a dead end.
I know that! I don't need you telling me!
Hey. What the hell has your
problem been all this time?
Nothing.
Nothing, my ass!
I asked you what your damn problem is!
I'm busting my ass here, and
you keep clicking your tongue!
I can hear you, you know!
So what's your problem?! Huh?!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Just calm down, both of you!
There's no need to get so—
Shut the hell up!
Can't you see Ram and I
are talking right now?!
Well, go on! If there's something
you wanna say, let's hear it!
I'm all ears!
You're very eager to keep
moving forward, aren't you?
Damn straight I am!
Why the hell do you think
we've come this far?!
So we can see the Sa—
Wrong.
We didn't come here to see the Sage.
What?!
We came here to wake Rem.
I came here to remember my little sister.
And yet what are we doing now?
Rem isn't even here.
We're just wandering aimlessly down here.
Stop playing games.
I'm not playing games!
I can't help that we ended up here!
When we fell down here,
why did you grab me and not Rem?
I'm sure all you could think about
was what lay immediately ahead.
You're always like that.
All you ever think about is
Lady Emilia and Lady Beatrice.
What kind of man are you?
I feel bad for Rem.
Shut up.
Didn't Rem believe in you?
Shut up!
No, I will not!
You don't actually care
about Rem at all, do you?!
Cut the shit!
Invisible Providence.
Quit screwing with me!
This is all your fault!
Your fault! Your fault! Your fault!
Just die, you bitch!
It makes me sick to think that
you look so much like Rem!
What?! I can't hear you!
If you've got something
to say, say it so I can...
...ra.
Magic?!
Look, bitch! It's too late to
come crying and say you're sorry!
That's my line.
You don't deserve to see Rem.
I'll slice you apart and
leave you here to rot!
Keep talking!
All right, that's enough.
There was no stoppin' you two,
so I had to decide who'd be more useful.
Do forgive me.
Why... did you...
What? You're askin' me that?
I could see things were gonna
end poorly, so I helped you.
Or are you pissed 'cause
I took your prey from you,
and now you're comin' for me?
Fine. I'll let you smooth talk me for now.
That's the way.
Very clever! I'm relieved!
So here.
A handshake to show we're gonna
make up and play nice from now on.
Natsuki?
What's wrong?
Oh...
nothing.
In that case...
L-Let me go! Let me go!
No! I don't wanna die!
You're already dead! I can't help you!
Damn it, you idiot!
Just die already!
Don't... leave... me...
It's Ram... Ram's magic.
That bitch... survived...
Patrasche?
You're alive?
Is Ram dead?
No, it doesn't matter.
Let me ride you.
Did you hear me?! Hey!
Get over here, damn it!
Who do you think I am?!
Finally, you're listening...
Barusu. Barusu.
Wake up before I burn your eyelids off.
I'm...
Barusu?
How pathetic.
Don't bite me.
Thanks. I'm okay now.
Oh? Well, I'm glad you're happy now.
Hey, come on...
Oh, thank goodness!
I see you're awake too, Natsuki.
Thankfully. How did the surroundings look?
Not good. I didn't see an exit
or any of the others close by.
Natsuki?
What's wrong?
Hey... just what is the miasma, exactly?
Huh?
This place is part of the dunes, right?
And there's supposed to
be miasma here, right?
Miasma is, in essence, tainted mana.
Tainted mana?
They say if you get stuck in it,
it'll eat away at your body and mind.
Is there a way to fight it?
Our gates take in mana by nature,
so all we can really do is stay away
from where the miasma's thickest.
The miasma did that.
So if we keep moving,
it'll happen again...
No.
Barusu?
Let's go.
Left. We'll go left.
Lady Anastasia, the ceiling's low here.
Be careful.
Right, got it. Thank ya kindly.
Ram, the footing's unstable here.
Watch your step.
Yes, understood.
If you get cold, speak up.
I'll lend you my cloak if you want it.
Wh-What? What's wrong?
That's my question.
Why the creepy considerate act?
What are you plotting?
I'm not plotting anything!
I just... want you both to
stay healthy, that's all...
Pervert.
That's not perverted!
How is this any different
from how Julius acts?!
Well, it's natural when Julius does it,
but from you, it feels...
sick? It's unnatural.
Did you say "sick"?!
Hey, do you smell somethin' funny?
It smells like something is burning.
A smell?
I'll check it out.
If anything happens,
we're leaving you as bait.
Don't hold it against us.
You know I'm gonna curse you if you do!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
That idiot!
El Fura!
Get up! You want to make Rem cry?
Don't you dare die, Barusu!
Invisible Providence!
El Fura!
Barusu!
Why...
Because Rem would cry.
Move, idiot!
This is not the time to lie around!
Get up! Get up, Subaru Natsuki!
Ram!
I found you.
The Keeper of the Watchtower